let's discuss the solution for our iron
law quiz the execution time is number of
instructions in the program three times
ten to the ninth which is three billion
times cycles per instruction in this
case x 2 and x the clock cycle time now
note that we have here three gigahertz
which is how many clock cycles we have
per second
what we need is how many seconds per
clock cycle so the clock cycle time is 1
over 3 billion make sure you remember
that this should here be clock cycle
time usually we express processor clocks
in terms of clock frequency which is 1
over time and conveniently these two can
be crossed out and we get 2 seconds so
the execution time is 2 seconds